

Mohamad Sina Kheiri

Front-End Developer(Next.js/React.js)

As a **Next.js/React.js developer** with **4 years of experience** in **frontend development**, I possess a diverse skill set of **25+ technical abilities**. With a strong focus on delivering **high-quality code** and **exceptional user interfaces**, I am committed to staying **up-to-date** with the latest industry trends and best practices.

I also have the knowledge and skills for UI Design and I have created **User personas**, **Wireframes**, **High fidelity projects** and **Prototypes** using **Figma and Adobe XD**.

- sinakheiri.dev@gmail.com
- +989100056440 (Telegram and Whatsapp)
- 🧿 Karaj County, Alborz Province, Iran
- https://sinakheiridev.ir
- https://github.com/IWarwolfl
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamad-sina-kheiri

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end(React.js/Next.js) Developer

Remote in Exmodules (<u>website</u> - <u>twitter</u>) 2023 - now

- **Led a team** of developers and provided guidance on project requirements.
- Created seamless user interfaces for various projects (+10).
- Learned and improved skills in Next.js,
 TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS.

Front-end(React.js) Developer

Full-time in Agahpadidar (<u>linkedin</u>) 2021 – 2023

- Established connections to Restful APIs using Async Thunks and Axios.
- Utilized **Github** for version control and collaborated with team members to resolve conflicts.
- Participated in Agile development
 methodologies such as daily stand-ups and sprint planning.

SKILLS

- Programming languages

Javascript, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS

- Frameworks

Next.js, Material UI, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap

- Testing

Vitest, Jest

- Libraries

React.js, Axios, Formik, Yup, Recharts.js, Jquery

- UI Design

Figma, Adobe XD, Responsive Web Design, Adobe Illustrator

- Other

Git, Github, Agile Methodoligies, Clean Code Principles,

PROJECTS [viewable by attached links and code is available in my github]

- Farzam.at[Front-end Development(Next.js - ts)]

Farzam.at is a startup project for design and coding services that I have collaborated on.

Frontend Developer and UI Designer

Freelance in ponisha(<u>link</u>)

2018 - 2021

- Designed **User interfaces** for mobile apps and websites.
- Created User personas, Wireframes, High fidelity designs, and integrated Prototyping.
- Developed static web pages and HTML templates.

EDUCATION

Islamic Azad University Of Karaj

Bachelor Degree, Computer Software Engineering

2022 - present

Shahid Beheshti University

Associate degree, Biomedical Engineering 2019 – 2022

LANGUAGES

Persian(mother tongue)
English(Advanced)

- Portfonext[Front-end Development(Next.js - ts)]

Portfonext is my personal **portfolio** project that is currently under development.

It showcases my abilities in **front-end development**, **UI design** and **up-to-date technologies**.

- <u>Bluetek</u> [Front-end Development(Vanilla)]
- Blue Wallet [UI/UX Design]

As a key contributor to the Bluetek project, I designed and developed 5 unique landings and profiles and I app that were both **visually appealing and user-friendly** and met the requirements of a **crypto-based** website and app.

- Modernist [Front-end Development(Vanilla)]

Modernist is a personal project that showcases my expertise in designing a **Customizable HTML Template**.

- Park Speedy [UI/UX Design]

Park Speedy is a Figma project that showcases my **UI/UX design** skills for a startup app aimed at solving parking space issues.

- <u>Academy Hamrah</u> [UI/UX Design]

Designed and developed a responsive UI/UX for Academy Hamrah's game developing event using Figma.